<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tyler Arnold</title>
    <link>http://blog.tylernol.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tyler Arnold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 10:29:54 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.tylernol.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Timeframer 1.03, AKA gimme your money</title>
      <link>http://blog.tylernol.org/posts/timeframer_1_0_3_gimme_your_money/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 10:29:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.tylernol.org/posts/timeframer_1_0_3_gimme_your_money/</guid>
      <description>the only change in this version is the ability to subscribe for a criminally cheap $ 0.49/ month to support the removal of ads and better support my ability to continue writing apps like this. Google Ads are weak sauce and I would much rather users experience the app without intrusive advertisements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timeframer ripped off by Instagram </title>
      <link>http://blog.tylernol.org/posts/timeframer_ripped_off_by_instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 17:28:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.tylernol.org/posts/timeframer_ripped_off_by_instagram/</guid>
      <description>Seems a wee bit similar to my app idea. 🤔
Instagram Stop Motion</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timeframer 1.03 submitted</title>
      <link>http://blog.tylernol.org/posts/timeframer_1_0_3_submitted/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 11:36:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.tylernol.org/posts/timeframer_1_0_3_submitted/</guid>
      <description>Ducky   Version 1.03 of Timeframer app has been submitted for review. The only new feature in this release is a monthly $0.49 subscription option to remove ads and support a starving independent developer..
Timeframer App</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timeframer 1.02</title>
      <link>http://blog.tylernol.org/posts/timeframer_1_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 14:33:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.tylernol.org/posts/timeframer_1_2/</guid>
      <description>Ducky   Version 1.02 of Timeframer app has been submitted for review. The primary new feature in this release is the loopback/boomerang effect that can be enabled in the edit view.
Timeframer App</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timeframer 1.01</title>
      <link>http://blog.tylernol.org/posts/timeframer_1_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 08:23:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.tylernol.org/posts/timeframer_1_01/</guid>
      <description>I have had 1.01 of Timeframer in the app store for over a week, 1.02 should be getting pushed up there within a few days. The major feature to 1.01 is the alpha blending feature, that enables the user to compose photos that line up more easily with prior photos in the time sequence. I intend to make some more improvements to this feature in a future release, but am adding other features and fixes before that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel 2 ships with a disabled image processing SOC</title>
      <link>http://blog.tylernol.org/posts/pixel2_soc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 11:05:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.tylernol.org/posts/pixel2_soc/</guid>
      <description>Kudos to Google for making progress on their own chip designs, but it is strange to ship a product with a disabled piece of hardware this significant. I suspect it will not be enabled for some time and perhaps never enabled due to some untested bug they found as they try to integrate it after it has shipped.
Pixel Visual Core</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analogue Super NT</title>
      <link>http://blog.tylernol.org/posts/analogue_super_nt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 14:37:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.tylernol.org/posts/analogue_super_nt/</guid>
      <description>I missed the release of Analogue&amp;rsquo;s original Nintendo emulator, but the Super Nintendo version is a more reasonable price point. Rather than a software emulator of the original hardware, this is a hardware emulator/reproduction of the original SNES hardware in an Altera Cyclone FPGA. So theoretically, this hardware is completely identical to the original, which should make a difference for 100% faithful game timing and sounds, with additional provisions for supporting modern screens.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>